(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
-Hey, man!
-Please!
Is this really the only CCTV
that you can hack?
Why, what happened?
-He already had Mikoy kidnapped.
-Huh?
What the hell are you doing?
In Tagalog… What are you doing?
I’m sorry.
Why didn't you tell me
that you're from a rich family?
Does something have to change
just because my status in life is higher?
It's just that I met a girl.
She’s the daughter of one
of the richest families
here in Prague. That level!
I want to open my heart for you.
I’m ready to make it work.
…Mr. Mikoy D. Pinagpala.
So, tomorrow you'll go
straight to the villa?
Just give Mom and Dad a chance.
They just want to meet you.
All right.
let's just meet tomorrow?
Okay.
All right. Get in now.
Aren't you riding with me?
I can drop you off.
No, it's okay. I’m fine. I'll just walk.
My place is just nearby, anyway.
Okay.
Just avoid Nerudova.
Huh? Why?
That's my shortcut.
And besides,
Prague is a very safe city. Right?
But tonight…
there's no moon.
Why are you getting nervous?
I'm not! Not at all.
Seriously, you’re like your father.
All right, get in now.
Okay.
All right, see you!
I thought you were a ghost.
Now I know why Chiara fell for you.
Filipino?
And I'm afraid you need to come with me,
Mr. Mikoy D. Pinagpala.
You’re crazy.
Oh… Who are you?
Just relax. Sit down.
Just call me "Sianong" for short.
To make it sound more friendly. Right?
Okay.
What do you need from me?
Look, we’re not bad people.
The fact that you're not tied up
and free to go.
But we really need your help.
We know about
your relationship with Chiara.
And we want to use your unique situation
because we're investigating
the Valtrovi’s.
Viktor Valtrovi.
Investigation?
For what?
In Tagalog… What are you doing?
This is a joke!
Sir Viktor is really playful, huh?
He's really good at pranks!
You're so crazy, Sir Viktor!
You always like joking with me!
Do you know, son,
a congressman was killed here?
He’s Partylist Congressman Salazar.
No history of corruption.
No campaign contributor
who’s a contractor.
And the only "crime" of Celestino Salazar
was that he started investigating
all the criminal activities
of the Moraviano Syndicate,
which is headed by Viktor Valtrovi.
And we strongly believe
the order directly came from him
to get Celestino killed.
Of course, he doesn’t want
everything he does in the Philippines
with his syndicate to be exposed.
I know it's hard to believe.
But this is not a joke!
This is serious, Mikoy!
That is why we're coming to you.
With your relationship with Chiara,
we now have a way to get close to Viktor.
To gather evidence against him.
And to build a case against him.
So he can pay for his crimes.
You are the only key
to bringing down the Moraviano.
Do you think
I would believe you?
And if what you're saying is true,
Chiara has nothing to do
with her family’s mess.
She shouldn't be dragged into this.
But she’s using
her parents’ money and wealth.
So, it means she’s involved.
In short, she’s a nepo baby.
First of all, you kidnapped me.
Second, why should I believe you?
For all I know,
you might actually be the syndicate,
and all your stories are made up
just to ruin them.
If you're not bad people,
then can I leave now?
Wait, you forgot something.
Again?
I'm Special Agent Alexandria.
And we want to use your unique situation.
We've been watching you.
Could you help us, Mr. Pinagpala?
What was that?
Was it a nightmare?
He fell down the stairs. Dead!
Nice one!
His name is
-Don Vito.
-Vito!
Okay! We already know that one! Okay!
I don't even know why
I ended up liking him.
Yes. Actually, the stories
of Sir Viktor are funny.
-I will marry him!
-Hey!
Is it okay that I already
introduced you to Mom and Dad?
Isn’t it too fast?
Uhm, not really.
It's not a problem.
That's how it should be, right?
Well, they seem to like you.
But sometimes
I don't understand them.
Yes, they're my parents,
but sometimes, it feels like
I don't know them.
What do you mean you don't know them?
Well, for example, you.
My mom and dad don't trust people easily.
But for some reason,
you won them over immediately.
Are they really like that?
They don't trust people easily?
It comes with the territory.
Given their status in life,
they have many enemies.
That's why they are very protective of me.
Because not everyone who approaches me
has good intentions.
Who's there?
What are you doing here?
I knew it. That wasn't a nightmare!
You kidnapped me last night.
And now, you just walked
into my house without permission!
Who knows?
You might even take
advantage of me while I'm asleep.
I apologize for our method.
But you must understand,
the Valtrovi are not simple enemies.
We have to move quietly.
Because if they sense
that we’re investigating them,
Do you still not believe us?
How am I supposed to believe you?
You haven't even shown any evidence.
All you have are accusations and all talk.
Help us to build a case
against the Moravianos.
So we can gather evidence
against Chiara's family.
You know what? Chiara is a good person.
She doesn't deserve
that just as our relationship is starting,
I'm already lying to her.
And honestly,
they're a little bit weird
and a little sketchy, but…
they're actually kind people.
Because if we’re wrong,
and they really have nothing to do
with the Moravianos,
then there is nothing wrong
if you help us investigate them.
Think carefully about it, Mikoy.
Because you are the only one
who can help us
to uncover the truth.
You know, buddy,
what you’re doing is dangerous.
We have no choice.
Only Mikoy can be used
to infiltrate the Moraviano family.
But how can you be sure
that we can trust this Mikoy?
How can you be sure
that he hasn’t told his girlfriend yet?
We might not get out alive
here in the Czech Republic.
And instead of the Czech, we end up dead!
Which begs the question,
why hasn’t Mikoy told Chiara about us yet?
Of course!
If you have a new relationship
with your boyfriend,
would you first ask him,
"Hey, sweetheart, is your family
part of a big syndicate?"
Because you might get punched
and then break up immediately.
Or maybe deep inside,
he is suspicious as well.
Deep inside,
he’s not sure about
Chiara’s family either.
I don’t know.
Are you thinking what I’m thinking?
Fried chicken with IU.
Yes, B1!
I'm hungry, and I've been
waiting for a while.
No.
Then what?
I can’t read everything in your mind.
I’m an agent too, buddy.
Just like you, okay?
I’m not a mind reader.
Okay.
And that is
if the job you give them
is close and important to their life…
their loved ones.
What do you mean by that?
Mikoy isn’t just a good family member.
He is the ultimate
brother.
I want to introduce you to someone.
It’s Angelito.
Angelito…
The intelligence of my friend
is not artificial,
but pure, old-fashioned hard work.
It means
diligence and perseverance-studying
in the library and reading.
We don’t really do that.
So, bro,
take a break from the library today,
and come with me.
Because we’re going to have
an end-of-semester celebration…
tonight.
So I can make it up to you for everything
you’ve done for me this sem.
Girls, hop in. Bro, let’s go.
Come on!
No more buts!
You deserve to have fun.
Let’s go!
Hello? I’ve already seen him.
You already know what to do.
GOOD MORNING, CHIARA
HAVE A NICE DAY
FOR SURE IT WILL BE BECAUSE OF YOU
Bro! Hey! Just relax.
This is our celebration.
-Our sem is ending.
-Hey!
Give it to us!
Give it to Angelito!
He needs to try it!
Try this one. Have a drink.
Angelito D. Pinagpala!
This is the police! No one escapes!
Get down!
Down!
Get down! No one escapes! You! Down!
But we have reasons to believe
that Viktor has tapped your phone.
And he is monitoring all your calls.
No one can tap this phone.
That’s why I can only call you here.
Won’t you stop bothering me?
What else do you need?
We need to talk.
There’s something you need to know.
Looks like he’s the mastermind!
You stand up!
-Put your hands up!
-No, sir--
It wasn't me!
I am still a student!
-Search his pockets!
-No!
-What is this?!
-Sir…
-That’s not mine!
Am I not clear enough?
I don’t want to be part of your schemes.
This also concerns your brother, Angelito.
-Not me!
-This one here too!
That’s not mine!
-Come with us!
-Boss--
Let’s meet.
I need to talk to you again.
Hey!
It was Sianong’s idea to show you this.
That your brother was arrested
in a drug den and buy-bust operation.
Oh, really?
-What the heck!
-What do you mean no?!
Stop it!
I will tell Chiara the truth.
And I will tell her parents
what you’re up to.
You need to know something.
What do I need to know?